Thank you very much
for conveying the President's
questions, General Taylor.
You are right,
General,
a first strike against
the Soviet Union would indeed
be dangerous for urban
and civilian areas.
The
consequences could no doubt
be severe.
Although,
I am hesitant to admit
that I agree with
Agent Miller
who at this point
can be
considered a
deserter.
Anyway,
I assume our great
American long-range missiles
have developed significantly
and can now take quite accurate
aim,
can't they?
You are certainly better
qualified
than I am to
assess our capabilities.
In any case,
we should
check with engineers
about how European satellites
and mainland China
can be spared from
collateral damage.
There is no need
to jump the gun
on that.
As far as I've
observed,
the USSR
has still
not had much success
in landing this kind
of missiles with a
decent degree of accuracy.
I've come to notice
that there is much
infighting and disagreement
about the media
between the
Soviet Union
and its
satellite states.
There are still
media outlets which
refuse to follow
politburo's
agenda.
The committee
is furious
about their
-- what they call -
"anti-soviet"
and
"anti-social"
propaganda.
Also,
the KGB
is not exactly known
for treating opponents
with kid gloves.
Therefore,
I've been wondering for quite
some time now how
long they were gonna
put up with that,
but now
they seem
to tighten the reins
once and for all.
There are talks about
- and I quote -
"taking appropriate measures"
against these
publications
- whatever that might mean.
They do sound
quite determined, though.
Maybe there is
an opportunity
to take advantage
of public opinion here.
Regarding your
question
if the Soviet
Medium Range Ballistic Missiles
possibly threaten Europe,
well..., to be honest
I would not worry too much about it.
The chances of that are,
to my mind,
so remote that it is
scarcely worth considering.
If they really intend
a major aggression,
they won't do it
out of the blue.
They would rather
look for an
ambitious situation
that will make for a
good excuse.
The US must not provide
such a situation
under any circumstance.
Bear that in mind
when making decisions,
General!
That's all I have to say
for now.
Best regards to
the President.
God bless America.