Second Chief
Directorate
Sergei,
what are
you doing?
Slacking off??
If you
have nothing
to do,
then get
to the
control panel
and start
the counter-intelligence
measure!
I've
just received
word, that
an unidentified
American spy
in our
ranks is
trying to
pass information
to the
Americans.
Thankfully,
his connection
is unstable,
so a
bit of
signal interference
should do
the job.
Just press
the big
button in
front of
you if
he says
something that
better be
left a
secret of
our institution.
But don't
overdo it,
our power
grid is
weak,
and we can
only do
as much
interference
as we have
energy in
our batteries.
If you
run out,
you will
have to
wait for it
to slowly recharge
again.
Understood?
Alright,
I will repeat
it...
I will now,
make a
quick call
for you
to test
it out.
Censor the
part, where
I spill
critical intelligence
about my
lunch today.
Anya,
my beautiful wife.
How are
you doing
today?
Did you meet
the new
neighbors?
Oh
my day
was good
so far,
I mean...
except for
the food...
I had a
Kulesh-Soup
and some
ingredient
- I think
rabbit it was -
was not
so good
for my
tummy.
Yes, I would
very much
like that.
Your cooking
is the best!
Thank you.
God
bless mother
russia!
Looks like success!
You've censored
the part about
my lunch today.
So no more
slacking off!
Get started already,
I hear
the spy
is starting
to talk
at this
very moment.
What did
you do!!
The part
about my
meal is
still in
and perfectly
understandable...
By god,
I hope you'll
do a
better job
when it
gets serious.
Do you want to
try it again
or get started
with the
real thing?
Good luck.
God,
you have doomed
us all.
We will be bombed
and it
will be
your fault.
I am going to see my wife,
this is it...
You didn't
catch it
all, but
we should
be fine...
We caught
enough of it,
so that they
might disregard it
as untrustworthy.
Thanks for your service.
Excellent!
What they got
was pretty much
useless.
You did your job well!
Thanks for your
service.
What...
you pretty much
censored only the parts
that were not relevant at all
and left in
the bits
that gave them
information...
How?
How did
you do
so bad??
Are you trying to sabotage us?